Guide to the Architectural Drawings and Maps of Yale University Buildings and Grounds
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Architectural drawings and maps (not microfilmed), Series II
  - 22:134 Sarah Wey Tompkins Memorial (New Haven Hospital), Heating Plans (4) and Floor Plans (3), 1931-1932 (Folder 633)
  - 22:139 Morse House (30 College St.): utilities (3 drawings), undated (Folder 516)
  - 22:148 294 Oak St.: plan (1 drawing), undated (Folder 517)
  - 22:156 Lab for Animal Sciences [Surgery, Obstetrics and Gynecology, Lab for] (375 Congress), 1952 (Folder 570)
  - 22:162 Edward S. Harkness Hall [B. Ross House] (367 Cedar St) (2 drawings), undated (Folder 518)
  - 22:167 Laboratory of Epidemiology and Public Health (4 drawings), undated (Box 512)
  - 22:168 Laboratory of Clinical Investigation (5 drawings), undated (Box 512)
  - 22:184 Air Rights Parking Garage (60 York St), undated (Box 521)
  - 23:2 Southern Observing Station - Australia (2 drawings), undated (Folder 522)
  - 23:3 Bethany Observing Station (7 drawings), undated (Box 521)
  - 23: 67-81 Howe St., Survey. Copy, 1965 May 10 (Folder 631)
  - 24:4 Yale Preserve (1 drawing), undated (Box 521)
  - 24:12 Guilford Field Station (6 drawings), undated (Box 521)
  - 24:13 Yale Nursery (3 blueprints and 2 tracings), 1932 (Folder 592)
  - 25:1 Yale Field Stadium (proposed)
    - Scheme L study for stairs 1/8", 1908 November 28 (Folder 576)
    - Plan - No. 1 1/32", 1908 December 10 (Folder 576)
    - Plan - No. 2 with modifcations 1/32", 1908 December 11 (Folder 576)
    - Section through south stand 1/8", 1908 December 11 (Folder 576)
    - Section through north and west stands 1/8", 1908 December 11 (Folder 576)
    - Section through east stand 1/8", 1908 December 11 (Folder 576)
    - Sketch plan 1/32", 1908 December 18 (Folder 576)
    - Alternative sections though centre 114", 1908 February 22 (Folder 576)
    - Section with isacoustic curve 1/4", 1908 February 21 (Folder 576)
    - Section on goal line 1/4", 1908 February 21 (Folder 576)
    - Scheme K seating plan 1/32", 1908 November 20 (Folder 576)
    - Sketch for perspective NTS, 1908 December 20 (Folder 576)
    - Sketch plan ?, undated (Folder 576)
    - Section, 1908 December (Folder 576)
    - Section, 1908 December (Folder 576)
    - Section for perspective, 1908 December (Folder 576)
    - Perspective sketch, 1908 December (Folder 576)
    - Plan, 1908 December (Folder 576)
    - Plan, 1908 December (Folder 576)
    - Plan, 1908 March (Folder 576)
    - Section through stands, 1907 July (Folder 576)
    - Scheme L stgel construction, 1909 January (Folder 576)
    - Scheme K seating plan, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Plan, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme B ground plan (under seats), 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme B typical section, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme J typical section, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme K typical section, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme L plan, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme L typical section, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme M plan, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme M typical sectlon, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme N plan, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme A typical sectlon, 1908 September (Folder 576)
    - Scheme B typical section, 1908 September (Folder 576)
    - Scheme C typical sectlon, 1908 September (Folder 576)
    - Scheme D typical sectlon, 1908 September (Folder 576)
    - Scheme E typical section, 1908 September (Folder 576)
    - Scheme F typical section, 1908 October (Folder 576)
    - Scheme G typical section, 1908 October (Folder 576)
    - Plan, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Scheme 0 typical section, 1909 February (Folder 576)
    - Harvard Stadium plan of supports, 1908 November (Folder 576)
    - Plan and section, 1908 March (Folder 576)
    - Plan and section, 1908 March (Box 654)
    - Scheme L layout of stairs, 1908 November (Box 654)
    - Details of permanent.stands, 1908 March (Box 654)
    - Details of permanent stands, 1897 September (Box 654)
    - Details of portable stairs, 1897 September (Box 654)
    - General plan of grand stands, 1897 September (Box 654)
    - Elevation and section, 1908 November (Box 654)
    - Plan, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Plan, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme H seating plan, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme H ground plan (under seats), 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme typical section, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme J typical section, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme L plan, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme L typical section, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme M plan, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme M typical section, 1908 December (Box 654)
    - Scheme N plan, 1908 December (Box 654)
  - 25:2 Yale Bowl
    - 3 drawings, undated (Folder 526)
    - Wrought iron fence, undated (Folder 655)
  - 25:4 Yale Golf Course Clubhouse: rendering (1 drawing), undated (Folder 527)
  - 25:5 Lapham Field House: alterations (4 drawings), undated (Box 521)
  - 25:7 Coxe Cage: proposals and details (14 drawings), undated (Box 490)
  - 25:8 Dewitt Cuyler Field: plan of baseball field (1 drawing), undated (Box 490)
  - 25:9 Quonset Housing, Whitney Avenue, Pierson-Sage Sq., site plan, 1946 February 19 (Folder 637)
  - 25: J.M. Griest Woodland Co, 1917 November (Folder 837)
  - 26:3 Gales Ferry Boat House
    - Repairs (2 drawings), undated (Folder 531)
    - 1st and 2nd floor plans, 1914 (Folder 607)
  - 26:5 Bob Cooke Boat House
    - Drawing, undated (Box 490)
    - Plans for alterations to the Yale Boat House (Derby, CT), circa 1958-1971 (Folder 681)
  - 26:6 Intramural Boat House: details (1 drawing), undated (Folder 533)
  - 27:1 33 Whitney Ave
    - Structural Drawings (5) and Architectural Drawings (14), 1969 September 8 (Folder 656)
    - Plumbing and Electrical Plans (25), 1969 September 23 (Folder 657)
    - Mechanical and Electrical Drawings (25), September 23, 1969 (Folder 657)
  - 27:5 Winchester Hospital: elevation (1 drawing), undated (Folder 534)
  - 27:12 Animal Care Facility (4 drawings), 1967 (Folder 832)
  - 27:16 Ivy Manor (579-605 Prospect), undated (Box 679)
  - 27:24 Lewis Walpole Library (18 drawings), undated (Box 490)
  - 27:25 W. S. Lewis House: detail (1 drawing), undated (Box 480)
  - 27:38 Dwight Hall Camp: East and south elevations, Allan T. Squire, architect, 1927 November 5 (Folder 629)
  - 28 Changsha Laboratory Building; Murphy and Dana
    - Basement plan, 1916 October 11 (Folder 537)
    - First floor plan, Biological Dept., 1916 October 11 (Folder 537)
    - Second floor plan, Physics Dept., 1916 October 11 (Folder 537)
    - Third floor plan, Chemistry Dept., 1916 October 11 (Folder 537)
  - 28 Dormitory Building (Changsha, China); Murphy and Dana, 1913
    - Plans and elevations, 1913 October (Box 574)
    - Plans and elevations, 1913 October (Box 612)
  - 28:15 Hsiang-Ya Hospital (Changsha, China); James Gamble Rogers with Stanley Wilson
    - Plans and elevations, 1916 May 1 (rev. 1917) (Box 574)
    - Plans and elevations, 1916 May 1 (rev. 1917) (Box 612)
  - 90:23 University Development - Region 1 (1 drawing), circa 1887 (Folder 538)
  - 90:31 Proposed Medical School Development (1 drawing), circa 1915 (Folder 539)
  - 90:47 Pierson-Sage Square Development (2 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 90:53 Proposal for Cross Campus (8 drawings), 1929 (Folder 541)
  - 90:78 Nathan Hale Inn (41 drawings), 1929 (Box 542)
    - 90:53: New Cross Campus plot plans, James Gamble Rogers (3), 1929 (Box 911)
  - 90:83 New Haven Hospital (13 drawings), 1929 (Folder 543)
  - 90:180 Math Building Competition
    - Venturi and Rausch entry, 1969 (Folder 544)
    - Venturi and Rausch entry, 1969 (Folder 545)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Folder 546)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Folder 547)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Folder 548)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Folder 549)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Folder 550)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Folder 551)
  - 90:185 Whitney Avenue, undated (Box 851)
  - 90:190 Music Building (46 drawings)
    - Drawings, 1974 (Folder 552–554)
  - 92:2 Fire-proof Exhibition Room and Book Vault (1 drawing), undated (Folder 555)
  - 95 Maps of Yale
    - 1890-1900
      - Topographical map of the two blocks bounded by Prospect, Winchester, St. Ronan, and Highland. Tracing of an 1872 map, 1890 November (Folder 631)
      - Map of the New Haven City Burial Ground, 1897 (Folder 623)
    - 1900-1930
      - Proposed campus master plan, author unknown, circa 1905 (Folder 557)
      - Atlas of New Haven County, Conn., 1911 (Box 783, Box 785, Folder 781)
      - Map of University Avenue between Wall and Elm, 1913 May (Folder 638)
      - Blount Avenue landscaping, Olmsted Brothers, 1913 May 22 (Folder 557)
      - New Haven, Sewer Plan. Tracing, 1915 June (Folder 631)
      - 122-126 College Street, Albert B. Hill, 1915 August 23 (Box 909)
      - Chapel, York, Library, and High Streets, Albert B. Hill, circa 1917 (Folder 557)
      - Property map of the NW corner of Elm and High, showing utility lines and pipes, 1917 January 26 (Folder 638)
      - Property map of the SW corner of Wall and High, 1917 August 4 (Folder 638)
      - Plot plan of ducts and manholes, French and Hubbard, 1917 March (Folder 557)
      - Property map bounded by Cedar St,m Congress Ave., Rose, Palmer, and Broad Sts., Albert B. Hill, 1921 January 27 (Box 909)
      - Property at Temple and Wall Streets, A. B. Hill, 1921 October 25 (Folder 557)
      - Blount Avenue, A. B. Hill, 1925 October 26 (Folder 557)
      - Property bounded by Park, Elm, York, and Chapel Streets, Tyler Trust Association, 1925 December (Box 909)
      - Map of block bounded by Elm, High, Wall, and York streets, 1925 (Folder 572)
      - Northwest corner of College and Chapel Streets, Albert B. Hill, 1926 March (Box 909)
      - Survey of three properties bounded by Derby Av., Tryon St., and Maltby Av., with property owners listed as Yale University, Olga Fabian, and Giordano (no first name), 1926 June (Folder 637)
      - Map of property conveyed by Yale University or the Union and New Haven Trust Company to the City of New Haven for the extension of Grove Street, 1926 August 25 (Folder 638)
      - Yale University insurance maps, 1927 (Folder 803)
      - Yale University insurance maps, 1927 (Folder 805)
      - Yale University insurance maps, 1927 (Folder 806)
      - Parcel abutting Maltby Ave., Survey, 1927 June (Folder 631)
      - Grove St., York Square Place, Lake Place, Ashmun St., Dixwell Ave., property map, Blair and Marchant, 1927 November 9 (Box 909)
      - Yale property bounded by Mansfield St, Trumbull St., Whitney Ave., and Highland St., Blair and Marchant, 1927 December (Box 909)
      - SW corner of York St. and Tower Parkway, Property Map, 1929-1930 (Folder 631)
    - 1930-1950
      - York St. parcel to be acquired from the Louis Linder Realty Co., Property Map, 1930 February 10 (Folder 631)
      - Maps of Yale University and Sheffield Scientific School, 1931 (Folder 796)
      - Maps of Yale University and Sheffield Scientific School, 1931 (Folder 798)
      - Maps of Yale University and Sheffield Scientific School, 1931 (Folder 801)
      - Atlas of New Haven County, Conn., 1931 (Box 783)
      - Race courses on the Housatonic, V. B. Clarke, 1931 March 19 (Folder 558)
      - Map of the properties within the area bounded by Dixwell, Broadway, Elm, High, Grove, Ashmun, and Lake, 1932 (Folder 637)
      - Telephone conduits, Southern New England Telephone, 1932 February 4 (Folder 558)
      - Yale athletic properties, Alexander Cahn, 1932 December (Folder 558)
      - Yale, 1933 (Folder 558)
        Biographical / Historical
        Map designed and executed by A.C. Parrette and W.B. Cram; Copyrighted in 1933 by The Mill Hill Publishers.
      - Yale Campus, G. W. Carmalt, circa 1933? (Folder 558)
      - Yale Campus, "A.H.S. After W.A.D.", circa 1933 (Folder 558)
      - Yale Campus, "A.H.S. After W.A.D.", circa 1934 (Folder 558)
      - Property at 65-69 Broadway, Blair and Marchant, 1935 June (Folder 558)
      - Maps of New Haven and Environs, 2 copies, 1937 (Box 792)
      - Map of parcel to be conveyed by St. Anthony Trust Association to Yale University, 1939 December (Folder 638)
      - Property bounded by South, Park, Oak, and York Streets, Blair and Marchant, 1940 October 15 (Box 909)
      - Maynard Farm, East Lyme, CT, property map, 1941 June (Folder 631)
      - Woodbridge, survey of land to be acquired from Yale University by the State of Connecticut for the Wilbur Cross Parkway, 1942 June (Folder 631)
      - Service Bureau drawings record book, 1942-1967 (Box 825)
      - Grace New Haven Hospital, South, Park, Oak, and York Streets, Blair and Marchant, 1945 October (Box 909)
      - Contour map of intramural crew lagoon, after 1946 (Folder 558)
      - Map of Central Campus, showing university and affiliated buildings, including the Observatory and Medical School, 1948 (Folder 637)
      - College St. from Phelps Hall to Elm St., Engineering Office, 1949 December 18 (Folder 558)
    - 1950-1970
      - Closed circuit television lines, Engineering Office, 1953 October 12 (Folder 559)
      - Tunnel plan of Yale School of Medicine, 1954 March 10 (Folder 559)
      - Survey of Property bounded by Canner and Prospect, 1955 December (Folder 631)
      - Yale Campus, 1955 (Folder 559)
      - Yale Campus (with negative), 1957-1958 (Folder 559)
      - Map of block bounded by Grove, Prospect, Trumbull, and Hillhouse, 1958 May (Folder 638)
      - Maps of Properties, Tracings, 1960 (Folder 794)
      - Yale Campus, 1964 (Folder 559)
      - Campus map in color with heraldic shields, 1965 (Box 712)
      - Yale Campus (with negative), 1967 (Folder 559)
      - Physical Plant drawing room drawings numbers, 1967-1970 (Box 825)
      - Map of Shuttle Bus Routes, 1969 October 13 (Folder 631)
      - Whitney, Grove, and Temple, Division of Engineering, 1969 August 20 (Folder 559)
    - 1970-2000
      - "Green Line" map, 1970 (Box 713)
      - Street index map by City of New Haven, 1973 (Box 713)
      - Superseded zone tax map for Yale University in New Haven and West Haven, 1970-1976 (Box 909)
      - Tax maps with New Haven zoning districts (4 maps), circa 1976 (Box 711)
      - Tax map, 1980 (Folder 559)
      - Blueprint of tax map, 1980 (Box 713)
      - Aerial perspective map, circa 1980 (Box 423)
      - Insurance map, Johnson and Higgins, 1982 March (Box 423)
      - Yale-New Haven Medical Center (4 maps), circa 1982-1989 (Box 710)
      - Campus map specially printed for W. Woods by the University Printing Service, circa 1983 (Box 710)
      - Parking system map, circa 1983 (Box 710)
      - Access (handicapped) map, 1983 (Box 710)
      - Libraries at Yale, 1983 (Box 710)
      - Yale University Planning - Yale University Tax Map, 1990
      - Campus map used for secret report by university officers, circa 1995 (Box 778)
      - Computer generated campus maps (10), circa 1996-1998 (Box 711)
      - Yale University Planning - New Haven map include. Yale campus, 1999 (Box 749)
      - Framework for campus planning precinct maps - Cooper - Robertson, 1999 (Box 750)
      - Yale University Planning - Base Plan - central campus, 2000 (Box 749)
    - No date
      - Property map of the northern part of the junction of Grove, York, and Ashmun, undated (Folder 638)
      - Property map of the block bounded by College, Grove, High, and Wall, undated (Folder 638)
      - Copy of a map of the block bounded by Grove, Hillhouse, Trumbull, and Prospect, undated (Folder 638)
      - Enlargement of New Haven with map key by the City of New Haven, undated (Box 710)
      - Yale Housing Department map, undated (Box 710)
      - City of New Haven planning map index, undated (Box 711)
      - City of New Haven maps (8), undated (Box 711)
      - Yale University Planning - Campus Historic Designations, undated (Box 778)
      - Index for 1/40' tax map, undated (Box 711)
      - Yale University Guidelines for Comprehensive Planning Study (Box 749)
      - Yale University Planning - Yale Grid compared to survey grid on Morse/Stiles map (Box 749)
      - Map of the land owned by the City in the area bounded by Broadway, Tower Parkway, Ashmun, and York, with valuations and acreage, undated (Folder 638)
      - Map of the block bounded by Grove, Hillhouse, and the railroad line, undated (Folder 638)
      - Property maps of the Science Hill area (3), Undated (Box 909)
      - West Haven sports fields, Undated (Box 909)
  - 95:133 Map with notes on the early ownership of the land on the northwest corner of Elm and High Streets, by Hubert Anson Newton, circa 1850 (Folder 661)
  - 95:152 Map of block bounded by Chapel, York, Library, and High streets, 1926 (Folder 573)
  - 95:203 Yale Field
    - 1926 March 1926 March (Folder 611)
  - 95:243 High, Elm, College, Chapel streets, 1917 April 13 (Folder 609)
  - 95:346 Insurance maps
    - 1952, 1959 1952, 1959 (Folder 610)
  - 95:370 Central campus; Eero Saarinen, 1958 October 10
  - 95:430 Campus, 1968 (revised 1970 Oct)
  - 97 Charles Foster Kent House (Providence, RI) (8 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 97 Lewis S. Welch House (New Haven), Sturgis and Barton (1 drawing), 1902 November 25 (Box 423)
  - 97 Charles H. Warren (Lincoln St), Orr and Del Grella (2 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 97 Freshman Dorm at Trinity College (Hartford, CT), O'Connor and Kilham (1 drawing), 1953 (Folder 565)
  - 97 House at 130 Davenport (1 drawing), 1967 April 7 (Box 423)
  - 97 House at 421 Humphrey St. (1 drawing), undated (Folder 567)
  - 97 Two Libraries by A. J. Davis (1 drawing), 1828 (Box 423)
  - 97:2 Simeon E. Baldwin House (44 Wall St), L. Robinson (9 drawings), 1884 (Folder 561)
  - 98 "An Astronomy Building for Yale," R. H. Ferguson, B. Arch. Thesis (8 drawings), 1951 January (Box 423)
  - Unknown region/chronology
    - Blueprints for Yale School of Drama (6 drawings), 1925 (Box 680)
    - I-91 Trumbull Street connector, 1965 (Box 912)
    - Presentation panels of proposed renovation, landscape, and lighting projects, circa 1980-1990 (Folder 662–665)
    - Two floor plan drawings of laboratory of physiology, 1930 (Folder 653)
    - Yale Design Lab, York and Chapel, 1953 (Box 679)
    - Yale Electrical Distribution System, 1955 (Box 679)
    - Planting layout for Marsh Botanical Gardens, 1965 (Box 710)
    - Models of Structural Biology Center and New Haven (copies); notes on Kline addition, undated (Box 710)
    - Paul Rudolph drawing of married student housing, 1962 (Box 828)
    - 152 Temple St., Elevation (1) and Detail Plans (2), 1939 April (Folder 630)
    - Unknown, Detail Plan, 1933 December (Folder 630)
    - 59 Lincoln St., Site Map (1), Sketch of House (1), Floor Plans (9), Elevations (4), and Brochure (1), undated (Folder 630)
    - Yale Stop-Gap Theatre, Seating Plans (6), 1969 July - August (Folder 630)
    - Quadrangle at Elm St (Silliman College?). Plan. Negative, 1931 (Folder 630)
    - Laboratory of Zoology, Plans (4) and loose, 1912 December 17 (Folder 632)
    - US Conduit Distribution for Yale Fraternity Block, Plans, 1927 jan 19 (Folder 633)
    - Unknown, Sprinkler System Plan for Workshop, 1917 June 20 (Folder 633)
    - Unknown, Deflecting Magnet Assembly Plans (14), 1958 January - May (Folder 633)
    - Survey drawings of the building at 17-19-21 Dark Street, five numbered sheets, 1929 May 26 (Folder 634)
    - 38 Whitney Ave., Floor Plans, Elevations, Framing Plans, Site Map, 8 sheets, 1955 May 7 (Folder 634)
    - Pastor's Residence, University Lutheran Minister, Floor Plans for Demolition Work (2) and New Work (2), in addition to a Finish Schedule (1), 5 numbered sheets, 1967 May 22 (Folder 634)
    - Pastor's Residence (Lutheran), 3rd Floor Plan, 1971 April 4 (Folder 634)
    - Pastor's Residence (Lutheran), 3rd Floor Plan, 1967 May 22 (Folder 634)
    - 28 Whitney Ave., Front Elevation and Cross Section, 1955 October 27 (Box 521)
    - Business Building on Whitney Ave. (possibly #30), Basement-2nd Floor Plans, Framing Plans, Elevations (10), 1926 January (Folder 634)
    - 30 Whitney Ave., 2nd Floor Plan, 1970 April 6 (Folder 634)
    - 179 Linden St., 1st-2nd Floor Plans (1), undated (Box 521)
    - Dormitory Building #3 (Culinary Institute of America), Elevations (2), Floor Plans (3), Cross Section (1), 5/17/63. Revised 7/2/63 (Folder 656)
    - 74 Dark Street, Floor Plans (4), 1929 May 11 (Folder 636)
    - 185 Church St., Electrical Diagram, 1960 January 7 (Folder 636)
    - 379 Temple, Floor Plan (2), 1975 August 25 (Folder 636)
    - Temple Garage, 385 Temple St., site plan, 1942 December 22 (Folder 637)
    - Drainage plan for the Grove Street Extension between High and Broadway, 1927 March 14 (Folder 638)
    - Drawing of Proposed Student Dormitory Residences, 1957 November (Box 521)
    - Tracing of Proposed Student Development at Morton Lane, off of Curtis and Conrad Drives, 1958 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #1, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #1a, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #2, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #2a, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #3, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #3a, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - University Housing Sketch #4, 1957 February 21 (Box 521)
    - 1st and 2nd Floor Plans for Dormitory Housing, Scheme A, 4 room layout. Two sheets, 1957 December 20 (Box 521)
    - 1st and 2nd Floor Plans for Dormitory Housing, Scheme A, 3 room layout. Two sheets, 1957 December 20 (Box 521)
    - Yale Music Center (22 drawings), 1974 (Folder 832)
    - Yale University undergraduate housing (12 drawings), 1972 (Folder 833)
    - Proposed development for Yale dormitory housing, 1958 (Folder 833)
    - Proposed apartment houses, 1954 (Folder 833)
    - Art School, 1945 (Folder 834)
    - #16 York Square, undated (Folder 835)
    - Dormitory: doors, 1925 (Folder 838)
    - University Services Bureau Building, 1927 (Folder 839)
    - University Service Bureau Building alterations, 1927 (Box 911)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 839)
    - Miscellaneous details (Folder 645)
  - Non-Yale buildings
    - E Carleton Granbury Jr., Reed House (Guilford, CT), 1954 (Box 772)
    - Compton and Pierce Architects, Lin House, 1956 (Box 773)
    - T. Gorm Hanson, 1958 (Box 774)
    - T. Gorm Hanson, 1958 (Box 775)
    - Jeff Gold, American Urban Corporation, 1977 (Box 776)
    - Paul Rudolph, Harkavy Residence (Sarasota, FL) (Box 777)
    - Residence of Mrs. Helen M. Benedict, 1st-2nd Floor Plans (4), 1907 September 30 (Folder 636)
    - C.H. Miller residence, 1905 (Folder 835)
    - Noyes-Clark Homestead, Floor Plans and Fireplace Elevations (8), 1939 January 23 (Box 521)
    - Residence for Mrs. E. B. Whitney, 1st, 2nd, and Attic Floor Plans (3), undated (Folder 636)
    - First Methodist Episcopal Church, Plans (4), 1936 February 15 (Folder 656)
    - The Taft School, Preliminary Details for New Mains, 1960 November 22 (Folder 636)
- Computer files (Box 863)
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.